{
    "categories": [],
    "description": " Try to guess capital cities of all the countries in Europe. ",
    "difficulty": -1,
    "questions": [{
        "answer": "Paris",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "France"
    }, {
        "answer": "Rome",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Italy"
    }, {
        "answer": "Berlin",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Germany"
    }, {
        "answer": "London",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "United Kingdom"
    }, {
        "answer": "Athens",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Greece"
    }, {
        "answer": "Madrid",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Spain"
    }, {
        "answer": "Dublin",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Ireland"
    }, {
        "answer": "Moscow",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Russia"
    }, {
        "answer": "Oslo",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Norway"
    }, {
        "answer": "Vienna",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Austria"
    }, {
        "answer": "Brussels",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Belgium"
    }, {
        "answer": "Amsterdam",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Netherlands"
    }, {
        "answer": "Vatican City",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Vatican City"
    }, {
        "answer": "Copenhagen",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Denmark"
    }, {
        "answer": "Lisbon",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Portugal"
    }, {
        "answer": "Prague",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Czech Republic"
    }, {
        "answer": "Budapest",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Hungary"
    }, {
        "answer": "Warsaw",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Poland"
    }, {
        "answer": "Helsinki",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Finland"
    }, {
        "answer": "Luxembourg",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Luxembourg"
    }, {
        "answer": "Stockholm",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Sweden"
    }, {
        "answer": "Monaco",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Monaco"
    }, {
        "answer": "Kiev",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Ukraine"
    }, {
        "answer": "Bern",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Switzerland"
    }, {
        "answer": "San Marino",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "San Marino"
    }, {
        "answer": "Reykjavík",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Iceland"
    }, {
        "answer": "Sofia",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Bulgaria"
    }, {
        "answer": "Bucharest",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Romania"
    }, {
        "answer": "Minsk",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Belarus"
    }, {
        "answer": "Zagreb",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Croatia"
    }, {
        "answer": "Tallinn",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Estonia"
    }, {
        "answer": "Riga",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Latvia"
    }, {
        "answer": "Sarajevo",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Bosnia and Herzegovina"
    }, {
        "answer": "Tirana",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Albania"
    }, {
        "answer": "Belgrade",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Serbia"
    }, {
        "answer": "Andorra la Vella",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Andorra"
    }, {
        "answer": "Bratislava",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Slovakia"
    }, {
        "answer": "Vilnius",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Lithuania"
    }, {
        "answer": "Valletta",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Malta"
    }, {
        "answer": "Skopje",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Macedonia"
    }, {
        "answer": "Ljubljana",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Slovenia"
    }, {
        "answer": "Vaduz",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Liechtenstein"
    }, {
        "answer": "Pristina",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Kosovo"
    }, {
        "answer": "Chișinău",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Moldova"
    }, {
        "answer": "Podgorica",
        "category": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Montenegro"
    }],
    "quizLength": 45,
    "title": "Europe Capitals Quiz",
    "url": "http://www.jetpunk.com/quizzes/european-capitals-quiz.php"
}